cuil.com 2008-12-28

# Cuil - Your Privacy

## Effective Date: July 27, 2008

Privacy is a hot topic these days, and we want you to feel totally comfortable using our service, so our privacy policy is very simple: **when you search with Cuil, we do not collect any personally identifiable information, period. We have no idea who sends queries: not by name, not by IP address, and not by cookies** (more on this later). Your search history is your business, not ours.

More precisely:

### Logs

We do not keep logs of our users’ search activity.

### Cookies

Cookies are small files on your computer that websites create to store user preferences, such as language settings. Each time you visit a Cuil page, your computer’s cookies automatically provide Cuil with your preferences. You can change or delete your cookies anytime via your Web browser options.

We do not record the information in your cookies on our servers; your browser sends your preferences to us with each search request. This way, we do not store any personal information about you on our servers.

### Other Sites

Cuil’s role is to direct you to other websites that you are searching for. We do not control those sites even if you are directed to them via Cuil. We are not responsible for any of their actions.

### Uses of Communications

We value and encourage open communications. Therefore if you decide to email us personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, information about you or any other content that you may send to us) via our site, we may retain your communication and share its content with third parties (such as our contractors). We won’t spam you or sell this information, but do not send us communications via our site that you want to keep strictly confidential. Such communications are outside of the search service we provide our users.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

Cuil is completely committed to protecting your privacy and we’ll keep looking for new ways to do that. To help protect you, we might make changes to this policy. We’ll let you know about any changes by putting a notice on our home page, where you’ll see it clearly, 30 days before they become effective. If you find such revisions acceptable, you will indicate your agreement through your continued use of our search service or communications with us.

### Questions or Concerns

We are committed to investigating and resolving any questions and complaints you may have. We will periodically verify that the commitments made by us in this Privacy Policy remain implemented and to remedy any problems. If you believe that Cuil has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, or if you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please submit them to:

Privacy Policy Matters  
c/o Cuil, Inc.  
66 Willow Place  
Menlo Park, CA 94025  
USA 

We will do our best to address your concerns. If you feel that your complaint has been addressed incompletely, we invite you to let us know for further investigation. If we and you are unable to reach a resolution, we will settle the dispute exclusively under the rules of the American Arbitration Association (www.adr.org).
